REY PHILIP PANDI



pandi.reyphilip@gmail.com



+63-946-969-5566



93A P. Zamora Street, West Rembo Makati City, Philippines



https://pandirey.github.io/portfolio/

OBJECTIVE

I would like to contribute to your organization as a full-stack web developer, leveraging my ability to develop a web application using readily available web frameworks. With my passion for learning, I will be able to take part in empowering your team with my newly found coding expertise

SKILLS

Hard Skills

- Frontend: HTML, CSS
- Databases: MySQL
- Scripting Languages: PHP, JavaScript
- Frameworks: Bootstrap & Laravel

Soft Skills

- Punctual,
- Team player,
- Dependable
- Trainable

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

CAPSTONE 1: PHOTOGRAPHY

Nov 2018

- Photography is a simple website for photographer wannabe.
- Mobile Responsive Design.
- Environment: HTML, CSS, & Bootstrap.

CAPSTONE 2: CAPS2STORE

Jan 2019

- Caps2Store is a Doughnut Ecommerce website using PHP and MySQL.
- CRUD Operations.
- Environment: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, MySQL, Ajax & PHP.

CAPSTONE 3: FICTBOOKS

Jan 2019

- Fictbooks is an asset management website using Laravel framework.
- CRUD operation both for Admin and Users.
- Environment: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, MySQL, & Laravel Framework.

CAPSTONE 4: PANDI MANILA

Feb 2019

- Pandi Manila is a hotel and resort booking website.
- CRUD operation both for Admin and Users.
- Environment: MELN (MongoDB, Express JS, Laravel & Node)

EDUCATION

TUITT CODING BOOTCAMP

Nov 2018 - Feb 2019

568 Hours of intensive four months course

BS ECE / RIZAL TECHNOLOGICAL UNIV

1999 - 2005

- Bachelor of Science Major in Electronics & Communication Engineering
- Registered Electronics Engineer (License #: 0037010)

EXPERIENCE

Design & Estimation Engineer

Mar 2015 - Aug 2018

ZAMIL Air Conditioners

Design Engineer 2

June 2010 - Feb 2015

KYOCERA Circuit Design Philippines, Inc.

Team Leader & CAM Engineer

Aug 2006 - May 2010

IPGEN